Contact

F 119 second floor, Dilshad Colony, Delhi 110095, India 8595758153 (Mobile) abidikashif@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mohammad-kashif-b0a6aaa7 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

New Business Development Marketing Marketing Strategy

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Français (Elementary)
اردو (Native or Bilingual)
Español (Elementary)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Beginner in French and Spanish
Call centre sales training certificate

Honors-Awards

Top sales agent
Ten club of sales

Mohammad Kashif

Marketing and Customer Service professional. Problem solving attitude and passionate about helping people.

New Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

5+ years of experience in direct, phone and business development marketing. 5 years in customer service while having selling as a skill that assisted in other business activities simultaneously. Developed and currently working on polishing communication skills.

Experience

Teleperformance Senior Customer Service Executive March 2021 - Present (1 year 10 months)

New Delhi, Delhi, India

Interpreting languages (English and Urdu) for clients and limited English proficiency individuals or groups over the phone and on video. Building change and promoting diversity at the root level. KPIs include accuracy in communication, smooth flow of dialogue between the clients, bridging the cultural gap and client satisfaction.

Momo King Marketing Manager July 2020 - October 2020 (4 months) New Delhi, Delhi, India

Oversight of marketing and public relations channel. Assisting operations and supply chain manager. Made big changes to essential marketing functions in a short period of time. Financial instability of the start-up and my personal desire polish other skills will see me move to a previously established organisation.

Uber

Food Delivery Driver January 2020 - May 2020 (5 months)

Auckland, New Zealand

Collecting groceries and food to deliver around the city. Happy Corona Warrior and received many positive feedbacks.

Brand Developers Limited 1 year 6 months

Customer Service Specialist February 2019 - December 2019 (11 months)

Auckland, New Zealand

Researching customer case, planning, execution, delivering one-call resolution, managing queues and collecting feedback. Managing and handling escalations from overseas contact center. Thrived in team-based work environment and was recognized by the operations manager to be capable of handling more responsibilities. Empathetic and altruistic nature assisted me to get countless customer commendations during the job. But I did not enough patience required due to limited time allotted by the embassies for professional progress.

Sales Consultant
July 2018 - February 2019 (8 months)
Takapuna, Auckland

Lead generation and outbound sales. Maintained all important KPIs. The managers offered a role in operations which I would go on to accept.

Breo New Zealand Limited
Sales Consultant
May 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 3 months)
Auckland, New Zealand

Sales, customer service, marketing & promotion, store management, training, motivating and delivery of goods. Continued to work part-time while pursuing Post-Graduation and accepted full-time employment afterwards. Continued into the role until a better opportunity in sales arrived where I was going to learn the basics of lead generation and converting warm leads in a call-centre environment.

Self Employed
Content Strategist/Developer and Manager
April 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 1 month)
Delhi

End-to-end marketing, acquisition, consultation, research, planning, ideation, creation, service delivery and customer service. Saw tremendous success in just over a year of operating the business without any help. Right at the time I had started receiving recognition from people around me, I'd decide to pursue higher education in management. Which I'm glad this time I had a chance

to do so because it proved to be one of the most productive educational experience I had acquired. This time also saw me as a person introspecting and questioning life.

L.E.A.D

Management Trainee February 2015 - March 2016 (1 year 2 months) Delhi, India

Took complete care of human resource department, assisted business development and marketing functions. Initiated and motivated owners to promote digital presence of the firm. Successfully completed the internship and moved on to being self-employed.

AND Sales

Manager of Sales September 2014 - November 2014 (3 months) Auckland, New Zealand

Encouraging Kiwi businesses to switch power and telecommunication service providers during the day and residential customers during evenings. Managing and training teams to do the same. The new opportunity coincided with plans for my sister's wedding back in India. I decided to move back to my home town indefinitely.

Salmat

Senior Sales Agent January 2014 - September 2014 (9 months) Auckland, New Zealand

Lead Generation, Promotion and Selling of power to residential customers.

Home Direct New Zealand Pvt. Ltd.

Customer Acquisition Representative & Territory Manager
June 2013 - January 2014 (8 months)

Auckland. New Zealand

An all-rounder as an acquisition representative, debt collection agent, and hire-purchase marketer/salesperson. After I was promoted to the role of a territory manager, I was required to drive a mobile shop while managing a hilly territory. Being from the plains myself, I decided to move to an offer of permanent employment from one of the previous employers. The role also saw me having a spiritual awakening and deeper understanding of cultural differences between India and Asia-Pacific.

Salmat

Business Sales Consultant September 2012 - June 2013 (10 months)

Auckland, New Zealand

Selling VOIP, power and broadband connection to kiwi businesses. Sole salesperson to cover all New Zealand territories for the Vodafone B2B project. Later, while working on Mercury Energy B2B project as an assistant to the project manager, trained and managed a team of six agents country-wide.

MASSIMO CAFÉ

Kitchen Assistant

December 2011 - September 2012 (10 months)

Takapuna, Auckland, New Zealand

Whatever chef needs done. Cleaning, prepping, cooking. Restaurant maintained A-grade Hygiene and Service rating during employment.

Auckland City Oaks
Housekeeping Assistant
March 2012 - August 2012 (6 months)
Auckland, New Zealand

Keeping guests' apartments tidy while working in teams.

One touch solutions
Sales Representative
August 2010 - October 2010 (3 months)
Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

Selling cheap vacation accommodation to Brits and Irish. Salesperson with the biggest ROI during the first month on the floor. This role motivated me to learn other languages and cultures.

Education

Whitireia Community Polytechnic
Post Graduate Diploma in Management, Marketing (2017 - 2018)

Auckland University of Technology
Graduate Diploma in Business, Marketing · (2011 - 2012)

Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University

Bachelor's in Business Administration (BBA), Business Administration and Management, General · (2006 - 2011)